<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Benjamin Western</title><link>https://benjaminwestern.dev/</link><description>Recent content on Benjamin Western</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 22:17:51 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://benjaminwestern.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Place-holder-blog</title><link>https://benjaminwestern.dev/posts/placeholder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 22:17:51 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://benjaminwestern.dev/posts/placeholder/</guid><description>This is here so I can be sure blogs load. Many many more to come›</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://benjaminwestern.dev/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benjaminwestern.dev/about/</guid><description>Opinions expressed for this site are solely my own and do not express the views or opinions of my employer.
A Passion for the IT industry, in my opinion, isn’t something you pick up. You&amp;rsquo;re born with it. In my younger years, I was the king of pulling things apart and trying to understand what and how they worked. I didn’t know it back then, but I was performing a root cause analysis.</description></item><item><title>Badges</title><link>https://benjaminwestern.dev/badges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benjaminwestern.dev/badges/</guid><description> Google Associate Cloud Engineer Professional Cloud Architect Professional Data Engineer Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Microsoft 365 Fundamentals PowerPlatform Fundamentals Azure Administrator Associate</description></item><item><title>Certificates</title><link>https://benjaminwestern.dev/certificates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benjaminwestern.dev/certificates/</guid><description>Datadog Certificates: 2021 Datadog Technical Specialist 3CX Certificates: Basic Certified Engineer v16 Intermediate Certified Engineer v16 Advanced Certified Engineer v16 AWS Certificates: AWS for Microsoft Workloads Business AWS for Microsoft Workloads Technical Connectwise Certificates: ConnectWise Automate Service Technician Certificate ConnectWise Manage Engineer Technician Certificate Microsoft Certificates: Microsoft 365 Fundamentals Power Platform Fundamentals Azure Fundamentals Azure Associate Administrator Google Certificates: Associate Cloud Engineer Professional Cloud Architect Professional Data Engineer Professional ML Engineer (in-progress) Terraform Certificates: Terraform Associate (in-progress) Sophos Certificates: ET00 - Fundamentals Engineer ET01 - Sophos Central Overview Engineer ET10 - Enduser Protection v5.</description></item></channel></rss>